Subtitles & Sync By
FridayToker
[breathing deeply]
[sighs]
[bird squawking]
[phone beeps]
Hey.
It's me.
Are you coming down?
I know it's hard, Annie,
but we both have to deal
with it.
[burner clicks and flame whooshes]
What is that supposed to mean?
Yes.
I'm being responsible.
Okay, well, somebody has
to take care of everything.
And we're her children,
for God's sake.
Hold on.
[phone beeps]
I'm not going back
to that house.
Annie, we're both supposed
to be here.
Stop telling me
what I'm supposed to do.
Jesus, you of all people.
What does that mean?
What do you think it means?
When's the last time you used,
huh?
You know what?
Fuck you.
That was more than four years
ago, before I was pregnant.
Yeah, and fuck you too.
So now that you're clean,
you just forgot about
what she used to do to us?
You forgot how sick she was?
You know what?
I'm just so crazy right now,
okay?
I have Eva all on my own,
I have work,
and now I have to deal
with all this.
You know what, Nicole?
You want to forgive her, fine,
but I don't.
That's enough.
[phone beeps]
It's our mother's funeral.
Are you coming down or what?
[bird squawking]
[ticking]
[water bubbling]
[kettle whistles softly]
[electricity crackling]
[sighs]
[Whoosh]
[gasps]
[computer beeps]
Hey.
How are you?
Hi. Hi.
Fine.
Is Eva asleep?
I wanted to say hi.
Oh, really?
I just put her down.
I'm sorry.
I'm on a neighbour's signal.
I might lose you.
Can you just go get her, please?
Now?
Okay.
Okay, okay, hold on.
- Thanks.
- I'll get her.
Hey, honey?
Hey.
Hi, baby.
Can you see Mommy?
Mom?
Shit.
Can you see Mommy, baby?
Baby?
Can you hear me?
Shit.
Sorry.
Mommy said a bad word.
Can you see me now, baby?
No.
Can you see Mommy?
I can hear you,
but I can't see you.
[sighs]
I just wanted to say
how much I miss you.
I love you.
I love you so much, okay?
I'm gonna see you
in a couple days.
Baby?
Can you see me, baby?
Yes.
Can you see Mommy?
Mommy, who's that behind you?
[gasps]
[crickets chirping]
[door creaks]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[engine turns over]
Nicole?
Hey, Nicole!
Voicemail.
[phone beeps]
Hey, Annie.
Um, no one knows
Where Nicole is,
so could you just call me?
[phone beeps]
Hey, Annie, it's Liz.
Could you call me right away?
[phone beeps]
Annie, I just...
I am really Worried
about Nicole.
I don't know Where she is.
Please, just call me, okay,
and We'll figure this out.
Ah, shit.
Call Liz.
[phone line trilling]
Hey, this is Liz.
Just leave a message,
and I'll call you back.
Bye.
It's Annie.
I just got to my mom's house.
I don't know where Nicole is.
You know what that means.
Um, just don't freak out.
She'll show up.
She always does.
I'll try calling her.
Bye.
Call Nicole.
[phone ringing]
[thud]
[keys jingle]
[ominous music]
♪♪
[breathing deeply]
[clattering]
[gasps]
♪♪
[door creaks]
[rattling]
[whispering] Shit!
Nicole?
[glass shatters]
[glass cracks] Shit!
[groans]
Shit.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
Mom.
[melancholy piano music]
♪♪
Annie.
Liz.
Hi.
- Been a while.
- Yeah.
Um...
Hey, there.
You must be
Nicole's little girl.
It's nice to meet you.
You've never met?
No.
I mean,
I've seen 10,000 pictures
every time I check my email.
Auntie Liz?
Can I go look at the windows?
Yeah, honey.
Go ahead.
So, um, you still haven't heard
from her?
No.
Annie, it's been three days.
Yeah, but, I mean,
you know how she is.
She probably just
couldn't handle all this.
She'll-
she'll show up.
Yeah, yeah.
You want to get out of here?
Maybe go to my mom's place
or something?
I don't want to really
be there alone.
Yeah, I would love that.
[sighs]
Out like a light.
I think that time change
really threw her for a loop.
[bluesy rock music]
♪♪
[sighs]
I found these in my room.
I can't believe that I can
actually smoke in here now.
♪ Catch a falling star ♪
[coughing]
[laughs]
Oh, it tastes like I'm 15.
Let me see that necklace.
A cross?
You?
Believe it or not,
Mom gave it to me
when I was a kid.
I love it.
♪ Oh, seven sisters,
Won't you cry ♪
I can't even smoke in here.
I feel like she's gonna
try and stop me.
Was it really that horrible
for you guys?
Growing up with her?
You have no idea.
[chuckles]
Some people
just shouldn't have kids.
I don't think
you should say that.
I mean, there's a deep love
between a mother
and her children.
I think it's a beautiful thing.
Hmm.
Oh, is it the same deep love
that made Nicole take off
on her kid?
Annie.
We don't know what's happened
to her.
Yes, we do.
We've see this
over and over again.
This is what we do
in my family.
When times get tough,
we take off.
My dad did it,
whoever the hell he is
and now Nicole's doing it.
Then why did you come back?
[scoffs]
For Nicole,
because we're sisters.
♪ I love ♪
♪ Praying to the stars ♪
[ominous music]
♪♪
[whimpering softly]
[sobbing]
[door creaks]
[inhales sharply]
[moans]
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[clattering]
[ominous music]
♪♪
[groans]
[clanking]
Shit.
[exhales sharply]
[urinating]
♪♪
Liz?
[electricity crackles]
[ominous music]
♪♪
Liz!
[whooshes]
[screams]
[grunting and groaning]
♪♪
[screams]
[Eva crying]
♪♪
[crying]
Ah!
♪♪
[crying]
[We Wish You A Merry Christmas
plays in background]
♪♪
Hey.
Who's she?
That's Nicole Barlow's sister.
She's crazy.
I can't talk right now.
Yeah, I'll call you later.
All right.
Bye.
Annie, I'm Bill Creek.
I know you told your story
to a bunch of people,
but would you mind
going over it with me?
Why do you want to know
what happened to me?
I know your sister.
She's been in and out of here
a bunch of times.
I don't need another person
telling me I'm crazy.
Nice smoke.
You know what I do now
when I get the urge?
They told me you work
as a waitress.
What else do you do?
What do you want to do?
I don't want to make friends.
You remind me of my daughter.
She's a little bit younger
than you.
You guys-you guys
are a lot alike.
She's a real fucking bitch too.
[chuckles]
So where is she?
Your daughter.
She's up in Seattle.
With her mother.
It's a sad story.
Let's talk about
why you're here.
You show up at 4:00 a.m.,
claiming what you claim.
They send some people over there
to check it out
because you refuse to go back.
I'm not going back
to that house.
Your cousin's missing.
They find signs of a struggle.
So, Annie, let me ask you this.
What would any cop in the world
begin to suspect here?
Why are you talking to me,
exactly?
You came here looking for help.
Yeah.
Well, I don't need your help.
So you're just gonna take off?
Better not leave town.
' [sighs]
[door opens]
I'm gonna stick around,
but it's not because of you.
It's because I want to find out
what happened to Nicole and Liz.
Okay.
Here's another reason
to stick around.
She's upstairs.
[melancholy piano music]
[indistinct chatter]
♪♪
[crickets chirping]
[cell phone crackles]
[ominous music]
♪♪
[coins clinking]
[machine rumbling]
[sniffling and crying]
[crying]
[Woman screaming on television]
[applause]
[ominous music]
♪♪
[suspenseful music]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[pedal cranking]
[engine puttering]
[engine turns over]
[revving]
Hey!
You have to wear a helmet.
[engine puttering]
[breathing heavily]
[engine stops]
Merry Christmas.
[traffic honking]
[crying]
Are you finally ready to order?
Or did you have any questions?
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[lock rattles]
[door opens]
♪♪
[wall crumbles]
[doorknob rattles]
[keys jingle]
[lock clicks]
[door creaks]
[light switch clicking]
You okay to wait here?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[door opens]
[ominous droning]
♪♪
- Hey.
- [gasps]
[knife clatters]
♪♪
You lived 16 years
in this house.
You have no memory of this room.
♪♪
[breathing heavily]
I can see into the living room.
These are everywhere.
It's me and Nicole's room.
My mom, she wanted me
to find this place.
She guided me here.
There's something here
that can tell us what happened
to Nicole and Liz.
Annie.
It's gonna take a lot more
than that
to figure out where they went.
No, don't you understand?
I was led here.
I can take some pictures,
but that's about it.
Why don't you believe me?
[sighs]
[engine revving]
[throbbing industrial music]
♪♪
[knocks on door]
Giles?
We spoke on the phone.
You said that Stevie was around.
Sit down.
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[mumbling]
What?
[shouting]
Are you here to fuck with her?
No!
Come on.
♪♪
Stevie?
Do you remember me?
Annie Barlow, from high school.
Oh, yeah.
Annie Barlow.
I just got back from San Pedro,
and I thought of you...
Can you really do that thing
that everyone says you can do?
[ominous music]
♪♪
[breathes deeply]
Take me to your mother's room.
[sighs]
I'm not getting anything.
Well, um, what do we do now?
Where do you think
we should go?
Down there.
♪♪
Don't touch her.
[electricity crackling]
Oh, she's here.
What's over there?
That's where
she used to take us
when we were bad.
Somebody's in there.
♪♪
[electricity crackling]
It's taking
all the fucking light.
She's taking all the light.
Be careful.
[breathing heavily]
[voice breaking] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry
for what happened to you.
What are you talking about?
I can see in there.
I can see what happened to you.
It's horrible.
[door creaks]
What's on the other side?
[door opens]
♪♪
Last flashlight.
What's with
all the flashlights?
Electricity.
It draws 'em out.
Hold this.
♪♪
There's a second presence.
[breathing heavily]
Oh, God.
Your sister.
What about my sister?
Oh, God.
[quivering]
Shit.
This is...
[quivering]
♪ This is where they go,
down below ♪
♪ This is where they go
when they go ♪
♪ It's where they go
♪ Down, down, down below! ♪
She didn't want anyone to know!
[thud]
Stay away from her!
[stuttering]
[gasping]
Damn it.
Can you help me?
Judas!
No!
' [grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[screaming]
Out now!
♪♪
Stevie. Stevie.
Stevie, who was that woman
in there?
Who was that?
She didn't want anyone to know.
Stevie, who's Judas?
Wait.
Why were you saying "Judas"?
She didn't want anyone to know.
Stevie, no,
but that wasn't my mother.
Who was that?
What happened to Liz?
What happened to my sister?
Stevie.
Ugh!
What do you think
you're doing to her?
[screaming]
Let me talk to her!
Open the door!
Stevie!
Stevie, what did you see?
God damn it!
No.
[engine turns over] Come on!
Shit.
[ominous music]
♪♪
[clicks]
[gasps]
♪♪
' [sighs]
[ominous droning]
♪♪
[wind blowing softly]
[birds chirping]
[melancholy piano music]
♪♪
[camera beeping]
[ominous music]
♪♪
[electricity crackles]
[rapping]
[light switch clicks on and off]
[ominous music]
♪♪
' Mom'?
[sombre music]
♪♪
Jennifer Glick.
Charles Barlow.
[thud]
[ominous droning]
[electricity crackling]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[blood spurting]
[drawer rattles]
Okay.
Charles Barlow, born 1947.
St. Baptist New Hospital.
And Judith Barlow...
Born 1950,
St. Baptist New Hospital.
This-
So my mother had a brother.
That's right.
[keyboard clacking]
I don't see anything on him
after the 1980 census.
[keyboard clacking]
All it says here is he worked
as a longshoreman.
Hello.
I want to talk to Stevie.
Is she around?
- Giles!
- No, listen to me.
Don't put Giles on the phone.
Just get her.
Okay, okay.
Hold on.
Hi, Annie.
Stevie.
I need your help
Um...
That woman in the house,
she was killed a long time ago.
And she was someone
that my mom knew, and...
What did you feel in that house?
The presence told me
that your mother did something...
Something that she didn't want
anyone to know about.
But this thing was trying
to kill us, wasn't it?
No, it was trying to show us
something.
Once you understand
what it Wants you to know,
you'll be free of it.
But how am I supposed
to understand?
I mean, what the hell
am I supposed to do?
I just want to know
what happened to my sister.
Annie, loan give youatoo!
To communicate
with the other side, but...
You should only use this
if you're ready to go
all the Way with this thing.
This woman who your mother knew,
do you have anything of hers?
Yeah.
You've got to go back
in the house.
If I do this, you promise me
that it'll leave me alone.
Trust me.
Okay.
Tell me what to do.
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[lighter clicks]
[necklace jingles]
Are you...
Jennifer Glick?
[whooshing]
[breathing heavily]
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
[breathing heavily]
Okay-
Okay...
Okay. Okay.
[breathes deeply]
What do you want me to know?
Judas.
Wait.
Um...
What.. what...
Was he my mother's brother?
Oh, God.
Um...
Uh, did he murder you?
Okay-
Okay...
I'm sorry.
Um, I'm sorry.
What do you need me to know?
Below.
[door slams]
[thud]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
[floor creaking]
[scraping]
[rattling]
[soft clattering]
[breathing heavily]
[whimpering softly]
[electricity crackling]
Oh, shit.
[rapping]
[breathing heavily]
[lighter clicking]
Okay, okay, okay.
[gasps]
[whimpering softly]
[sobbing softly]
[gun clicking]
[gun clatters on floor]
[door clicks open]
[shuffling]
[gun clicking]
[gunshot]
[ominous music]
♪♪
[groans softly]
[whimpering]
♪♪
[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
♪♪
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
Ugh!
♪♪
You fuckin' crazy
son of a bitch!
[groaning]
Just do it already!
[mumbling indistinctly]
[breathing heavily]
♪♪
[suspenseful music]
[grunting and groaning]
♪♪
[screaming]
' [groans]
♪♪
[moaning]
[screams]
♪♪
[groaning]
[gunshot]
[whooshing]
[shivering]
[sombre music]
♪♪
[dog barking in distance]
[crying softly]
[engine turns over]
[melancholy music]
♪♪
I'm gonna eat some
of your ice cream with you.
♪♪
Chicka-chicka-chicka.
[laughter]
♪♪
[breathing deeply]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
♪♪
[lively rock music]
♪ Come on, Periwinkle I
♪ Like a motorcycle
excites me ♪
♪ If you're gone
when I get back ♪
♪ I'll remember
all your faults ♪
♪ And hate you ♪
♪ Exploring inner universe ♪
♪ I'll saint you ♪
♪ Come on, Periwinkle ♪
♪ On my motorcycle excite me ♪
♪ If you're lost
when I get there ♪
♪ I'll remember all the times ♪
♪ And hate you ♪
♪ Couldn't ever wait too long ♪
♪ To take you ♪
♪ She'll disown you,
never stone you ♪
♪ Wanna glow in bliss dementia ♪
♪ Love kiss tongues ♪
♪ The way speed does you ♪
♪ Placid thumbs ♪
♪ On what's the way
to fuzz land ♪
♪ She won't want to
ever come to ♪
♪ Stays asleep
to not to worry you ♪
♪ And my cheek dismay ♪
♪ I'll drive you ♪
♪ To the place ♪
♪ I'll lay my head beside you ♪
♪♪'
♪ Truly gone,
you won't be back ♪
♪ Still can't seem to find
the time ♪
♪ To hate you ♪
♪ Love kiss
on your dying mouth ♪
♪ I'll take you ♪
♪ Take you ♪
[echoing] ♪ Take you ♪
Subtitles & Sync By
FridayToker